{"entrance":{"x":2,"y":7,"angle":0},"exit":{"x":6,"y":2},"grid":[[{"x":0,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":2,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":3,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":4,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":5,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":6,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":7,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":8,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":9,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":10,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":11,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":12,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":13,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":14,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":15,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":16,"y":0,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":1,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":3,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":5,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":6,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":7,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":9,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":0.5,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_14","left":"walls_0_14","back":"walls_0_14","right":"walls_0_14","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":1},{"x":10,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":0.5,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_14","left":"walls_0_14","back":"walls_0_14","right":"walls_0_14","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":1},{"x":11,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":0.5,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_14","left":"walls_0_14","back":"walls_0_14","right":"walls_0_14","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":1},{"x":12,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":0.5,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_14","left":"walls_0_14","back":"walls_0_14","right":"walls_0_14","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":1},{"x":13,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":0.5,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_14","left":"walls_0_14","back":"walls_0_14","right":"walls_0_14","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":1},{"x":14,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":0.5,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_14","left":"walls_0_14","back":"walls_0_14","right":"walls_0_14","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":1},{"x":15,"y":1,"blocking":true,"height":0.5,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_14","left":"walls_0_14","back":"walls_0_14","right":"walls_0_14","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false,"offset":1},{"x":16,"y":1,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":2,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":3,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":4,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":5,"y":2,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":6,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":7,"y":2,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":9,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":10,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":11,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":12,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":13,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":14,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":15,"y":2,"blocking":true,"height":0.5,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_14","left":"walls_0_14","back":"walls_0_14","right":"walls_0_14","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false,"offset":1},{"x":16,"y":2,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":3,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":3,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":3,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":3,"y":3,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":4,"y":3,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":5,"y":3,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"doors_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":6,"y":3,"door":true,"axis":"x","blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"doors_0_05","left":"doors_0_05","back":"doors_0_05","right":"doors_0_05","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"key":"red"},{"x":7,"y":3,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"doors_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":8,"y":3,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":9,"y":3,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":10,"y":3,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":3,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":12,"y":3,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":13,"y":3,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":14,"y":3,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":15,"y":3,"blocking":true,"height":0.5,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_14","left":"walls_0_14","back":"walls_0_14","right":"walls_0_14","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false,"offset":1},{"x":16,"y":3,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":4,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":4,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":3,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":4,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":5,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":6,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":7,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":8,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":9,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":10,"y":4,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":12,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":13,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":14,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":15,"y":4,"blocking":true,"height":0.5,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_14","left":"walls_0_14","back":"walls_0_14","right":"walls_0_14","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false,"offset":1},{"x":16,"y":4,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":5,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":5,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":3,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":4,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":5,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":6,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":7,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":8,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":9,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":10,"y":5,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":12,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":13,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":14,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":15,"y":5,"blocking":true,"height":0.5,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_14","left":"walls_0_14","back":"walls_0_14","right":"walls_0_14","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false,"offset":1},{"x":16,"y":5,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":6,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":6,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_18","left":"walls_0_18","back":"walls_0_18","right":"walls_0_18","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":6,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_17","left":"walls_0_17","back":"walls_0_17","right":"walls_0_17","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":3,"y":6,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_13","left":"walls_0_13","back":"walls_0_13","right":"doors_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":4,"y":6,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":5,"y":6,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":6,"y":6,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":7,"y":6,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":8,"y":6,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":9,"y":6,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":10,"y":6,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":6,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":6,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":6,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":14,"y":6,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":15,"y":6,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":6,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":7,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_18","left":"walls_0_18","back":"walls_0_18","right":"walls_0_18","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":3,"y":7,"door":true,"axis":"y","blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"doors_0_02","left":"doors_0_02","back":"doors_0_02","right":"doors_0_02","bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":4,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":5,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":6,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":7,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":8,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":9,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":10,"y":7,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":true},{"x":11,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":12,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":13,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":14,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":15,"y":7,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":7,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":8,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":8,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_18","left":"walls_0_18","back":"walls_0_18","right":"walls_0_18","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":8,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_17","left":"walls_0_17","back":"walls_0_17","right":"walls_0_17","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":3,"y":8,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_13","left":"doors_0_01","back":"walls_0_13","right":"walls_0_13","bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":4,"y":8,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":5,"y":8,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":6,"y":8,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":7,"y":8,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":8,"y":8,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":9,"y":8,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":10,"y":8,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":8,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":8,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":8,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":14,"y":8,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":15,"y":8,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":8,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":9,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":9,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":3,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":4,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":5,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":6,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":7,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":8,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":9,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":10,"y":9,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_12","left":"walls_0_12","back":"walls_0_12","right":"walls_0_12","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":11,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":12,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":13,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":14,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":15,"y":9,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":9,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":10,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":3,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":4,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":5,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":6,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":7,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":8,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":9,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":10,"y":10,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_12","left":"walls_0_12","back":"walls_0_12","right":"walls_0_12","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":11,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":12,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":13,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":14,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":15,"y":10,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":10,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":11,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":3,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":4,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":5,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":6,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":7,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":8,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":9,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":10,"y":11,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_12","left":"walls_0_12","back":"walls_0_12","right":"walls_0_12","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false,"offset":0.5,"transparency":1},{"x":11,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":12,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":13,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":14,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":15,"y":11,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":11,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":12,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":12,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":12,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":3,"y":12,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":12,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":5,"y":12,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":6,"y":12,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":true},{"x":7,"y":12,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":12,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":9,"y":12,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":10,"y":12,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":12,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":12,"y":12,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":13,"y":12,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":14,"y":12,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":15,"y":12,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":12,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":13,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":13,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":13,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":3,"y":13,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":4,"y":13,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":5,"y":13,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":6,"y":13,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":7,"y":13,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":13,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":9,"y":13,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":10,"y":13,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":13,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":12,"y":13,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":13,"y":13,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":14,"y":13,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":15,"y":13,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":13,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":14,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":14,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":14,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":3,"y":14,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":14,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":5,"y":14,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":6,"y":14,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":7,"y":14,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":14,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":9,"y":14,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":10,"y":14,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":14,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":12,"y":14,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":13,"y":14,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":14,"y":14,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{"bottom":"floors_0_03"}},{"x":15,"y":14,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"y","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":14,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":15,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":2,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":3,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":4,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":5,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":6,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":7,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":8,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":9,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":10,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":11,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":12,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":13,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":14,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":15,"y":15,"blocking":true,"height":1,"sides":{"front":"walls_0_01","left":"walls_0_01","back":"walls_0_01","right":"walls_0_01","bottom":"floors_0_03"},"axis":"x","pushable":false},{"x":16,"y":15,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}],[{"x":0,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":1,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":2,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":3,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":4,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":5,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":6,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":7,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":8,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":9,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":10,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":11,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":12,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":13,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":14,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":15,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}},{"x":16,"y":16,"blocking":false,"height":0,"sides":{}}]],"objects":[],"items":[{"type":"weaponitem","weapon":"pistol","x":7,"y":6,"name":"items_09"},{"type":"weaponitem","weapon":"launcher","x":5,"y":11,"name":"items_12"},{"color":"green","type":"keyitem","x":7,"y":11,"name":"items_03"}],"enemies":[],"sky":[{"x":22627.41699796952,"y":22627.416997969518,"distance":32000,"elavation":6000,"name":"gradient","repeat":true},{"x":5561.130685089525,"y":31513.073882173976,"distance":32000,"elavation":6000,"name":"planets_01"},{"x":-24182.050649274155,"y":20957.777229370942,"distance":32000,"elavation":6000,"name":"planets_02"},{"x":-6275.716324421891,"y":-31378.581622109443,"distance":32000,"elavation":6000,"name":"planets_03"}]}